Johnny Otis Collection, 1949-2012 SC 106
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 4. Radio Airchecks, Johnny Otis Show
  - 4.2. KPFK (Los Angeles) and KPFA (Berkeley), 1982-1994
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-06-04; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g84m60x31m
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Wilson Pickett, Sam & Dave, Julia Lee, Louis Jordan, Johnny Otis, Marvin Gaye, Jackie Wilson, Aretha Franklin, Little Walter, Memphis Slim, B.B. King, Billie Holiday, Count Basie, Jimmie Lunceford, Aaron Neville, and The Drifters. Otis talks about Aretha Franklin, Jackie Wilson, and promotes an upcoming B.B. King concert.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Little Richard, Big Joe Turner, Clyde McPhatter, Clovers, Lionel Hampton, Fats Waller, Preston Love & Shuggie Otis, Temptations, Al Green, Irma Thomas, John Lee Hooker, Duke Ellington, Nat King Cole, Robins, Chords, Fiestas, and Harptones. Otis talks about local blues radio shows.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-06-11; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2486; EC10 2487
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/9504951t9f
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Sam & Dave, Jessie Hill, Joe Tex, Big Joe Turner, LaVern Baker, Willie Mabon, Jesse Belvin, Bobby Bland, Ikettes, Pete Johnson, B.B. King, Little Willie John, Moonglows, Albert King, Louis Jordan, Muddy Waters, and Elmore James. Otis promotes upcoming gigs and talks about racism in America.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Guitar Shorty, Irma Thomas, Marvin Gaye, Otis Redding, Dinah Washington, Ray Charles, Chuck Willis, Lester Young, Billie Holiday, Johnny Otis, Stevie Wonder, and Aretha Franklin. Otis promos a Blues Society concert then talks about his upcoming concerts and his band's lineup.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-06-18; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Dewey Terry, Jimmy Espinoza, Tim "Zeke the Sheik" Dundon
      EC10 2488; EC10 2489
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b49425rn5k
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Junior Walker & The All Stars, Hank Ballard, Erskine Hawkins, Wilson Pickett, Little Willie John, Jimmy Reed, Sam & Dave, Chuck Berry, Mills Brothers, Lowell Fulson, Art Tatum, Bobby Bland, Etta James, Richard Berry, Lil Green, Jackie Wilson, Temptations, John Lee Hooker, and B.B. King. Otis talks about Erskine Hawkins, Etta James, the upcoming Blues Society concert, and the state of jazz and blues festivals today.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Dorothy Love Coates, Billie Holiday, Don & Dewey, Count Basie, Helen Humes, Howlin' Wolf, Muddy Waters, Midniters, and Bo Diddley. Otis and Terry talk about their new albums, who wrote "Koko Joe" and "I'm Leaving It All Up To You." Otis and Dewey talk about the Squires, the old days, Otis's TV show, and Dewey's influences. Otis and Jimmy Espinoza (of Thee Midniters) talk about R&B, early Midniters hits, the song "Whittier Boulevard," love ballads, and Chicano covers of R&B songs. Otis and Tim "Zeke the Sheik" Dundon talk about conservation and environment issues, cooperating with nature, and Zeke's giant compost pile.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: "Double Play" night, 1990-07-03; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Billy Vera, Ed Pearl
      EC10 2490; EC10 2491
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/118r371525
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of The Clovers, Ray Charles, Little Esther Phillips, Big Mama Thornton, Louis Armstrong, and Fats Domino. Otis and Pearl talk about the Ashgrove Theatre and an upcoming Pete Seeger concert. Otis and guests talk about artistry in past music and comedy, the problems with TV, and homogenization of many ethnic styles in the arts. Otis talks about President Bush and healthcare in the U.S.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of The Midnighters, Gladys Knight, Lowell Fulson, Otis Redding & Carla Thomas, Coasters, Alvin Robinson, Fats Waller, Count Basie, Nat King Cole, J. Otis, Dinah Washington, Percy Mayfield, Delta Rhythm Boys, and Duke Ellington. Otis and guests talk about cover versions, commercialism, their favorite composers, and Harlan Leonard.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-07-09; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Tim "Zeke the Sheik" Dundon, Tim Frank, William Smith, Manju Koshy
      EC10 2492; EC10 2493
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p38w32xj33
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Wilbert Harrison, Ramsey Lewis, Delta Rhythm Boys, Aretha Franklin, Percy Mayfield, Little Milton, Wilson Pickett, Ray Charles, Charles Brown, Sam & Dave, Chris Kenner, Soul Stirrers, Sam Cooke, Little Walter, King Curtis, James Brown, and Otis Redding.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Billie Holiday, Count Basie, Chuck Berry, Drifters, B.B. King, Joe Turner, Marvin Gaye, Ravens, Floyd Dixon, Temptations, Jackie Wilson, Fats Domino, and Lee Allen. Otis, Tim "Zeke the Sheik" Dundon and local college students talk about Zeke, his giant compost pile, and environmental issues.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-07-16; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Dewey Terry, Jerry Hudson, Brad Pie
      EC10 2494
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/w92435nq5r
      Otis plays the music of The Moonglows, Stevie Wonder, Junior Walker, Staple Singers, Swan Silvertones, Billie Holiday, Joe Liggins, Don & Dewey, Percy Mayfield, Otis Redding, Booker T & The MG's, Jimmie Lunceford, Count Basie, Jimmy Reed, Bobby Bland, and Little Richard. Otis promotes a local gospel festival and talks with friends talk about fishing. Otis and Terry talk about the Doo-Wop Society.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-07-24; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Floyd Dixon, Jimmy Espinoza, Brad Pie, Nicky Otis
      EC10 2495; EC10 2496
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f75r27477b
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Tommy Tucker, LaVern Baker, Big Joe Turner, Johnny Ace, Big Mama Thornton, Larry Williams, Little Richard, Roy Milton, Ravens, Marvin Gaye & Tammi Terrell, Flamingos, Muddy Waters, Jay McShann, Billie Holiday, Nat King Cole, Irma Thomas, and Earl King. Otis promotes the KPFK All Nations Gospel Festival and the Watts Towers Music & Arts Festival.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of King Curtis, James Brown, Floyd Dixon, Drifters, Ray Charles, Aretha Franklin, Jimmy Reed, and B.B. King. Live performance by Otis, Dixon, Espinoza, Pie, and Nicky. Otis and Dixon talk about the changing audience for the blues and when they first met.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-07-30; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2497; EC10 2498
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x51h543b83
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Hank Ballard & The Midnighters, Monotones, Staple Singers, Fontella Bass, Bobby Bland, T-Bone Walker, Richard Berry, B.B. King, Fats Domino, Elmore James, Jimmy Reed, Lee Andrews & The Hearts, Moonglows, Jimmie Lunceford, Billie Holiday, and Little Walter. Otis and friends talk about the KPFK All Nations Gospel Festival, playing at the Watts Festival, and the recent passing of singer and bandleader Bobby Day.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Little Walter, Don & Dewey, Dirty Dozens Brass Band, Clifton Chenier, Louis Jordan with Johnny & Shuggie Otis, Louis Armstrong, Temptations, Four Tops, Floyd Dixon, Joe Liggins, Sam & Dave, Johnnie Taylor, Little Esther & Mel Walker, Charles Brown, Ruth Brown, Duke Ellington, Ray Charles, Coasters, Lori Tate, Howlin' Wolf, and Bobby Bland. Otis and friends talk some more about Bobby Day.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-08-06; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2499; EC10 2500
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/880v73j280
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of B.B. King, Coasters, Charles Brown, Ruth Brown, Otis Redding, Aretha Franklin, James Brown, Muddy Waters, T-Bone Walker, Sly & The Family Stone, Jimmy Reed, Frankie Lymon & The Teenagers, Fiestas, Count Basie, Billie Holiday, Fats Domino, and Tony Allen & The Champs. Otis invites listeners to call in and vote for their favorite artists and then talks about Sly Stone.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Bo Diddley, Little Willie John, Louis Jordan & The Tympany Five, Ray Charles & Lily Ford, Duke Ellington, Dinah Washington, Clarence "Frogman" Henry, Shirelles, Art Tatum, LaVern Baker, Al Green, Harold Melvin & The Blue Notes, Big Joe Turner, King Curtis, Nat Cole, Slim Gaylord, and Billie Holiday. Otis gives results of the favorite artists poll and talks about his pet birds.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-08-13; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2501; EC10 2502
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x719607g8t
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Lowell Fulson, Eddie Vinson, LaVern Baker, Louis Jordan, Little Richard, Bobby Day, Four Deuces, Drifters, B.B. King, Aretha Franklin, Smokey Robinson, Jay McShann, Coasters, Gladys Knight & The Pips, Jackie Wilson & The Dominoes, Little Walter, Pee Wee Crayton, and Billie Holiday. Otis promotes upcoming concerts.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Ella Fitzgerald & Louis Armstrong, Fats Domino, Bobby Bland, Jessie Hill, Allen Toussaint, Otis Redding, Little Milton, Ruth Brown, Ray Charles, Count Basie, Dinah Washington, Lester Young, Shirelles, Bobby Day, James Brown, Duke Ellington, Johnny Otis Show, Marvelettes, Marvin Gaye, Wilson Pickett, and Jimmie Lunceford.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-08-20; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2503; EC10 2504
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v63f95qp1v
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Ray Charles, Dominoes, Etta James, Preston Love, Johnny Otis Show, James Brown, Big Joe Turner, Moms Mabley & Pearl Bailey, Percy Mayfield, Four Tops, Temptations, Jerry Butler, Aretha Franklin, Fletcher Henderson, and Billie Holiday. Otis talks about his new album with the Johnny Otis Show band.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Billie Holiday, Slim Gaylord, Nat Cole, Larry Williams, Flamingos, Dixie Cups, Wild Tchoupitoulas, Johnny Otis Show, B.B. King, Chuck Berry, Andy Kirk, and Count Basie.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-08-28; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2505; EC10 2506
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/593t84ft4m
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Bill Doggett, Coasters, Martha & The Vandellas, Stevie Ray Vaughan, Curtis Mayfield & The Impressions, Louis Jordan, Clarence Henry, Charles Brown, Floyd Dixon, Ike & Tina Turner, James Brown, Benny Goodman, Billie Holiday, Dorothy Love Coates & The Gospel Harmonettes, Wilson Pickett, Chuck Willis, and Ray Charles. Otis promos Floyd Dixon's upcoming gig and the Long Beach Blues Festival.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of the Johnny Otis Show, Chick Webb, Roy Eldridge, LaVern Baker, B.B. King, Frankie Lymon & The Teenagers, Imperials, Sly & The Family Stone, Sweet Inspirations, Count Basie, Julia Lee, Sam & Dave, King Curtis, Jimmy Nelson, Larry Williams, Little Richard, Smokey Robinson, and Don & Dewey. Otis tells a story about secretly liking "uncool" music in his youth.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-09-03; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2507; EC10 2508
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/395w231m00
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Louis Jordan, Hank Ballard & The Midnighters, Bobby Bland, Crows, Chords, Floyd Ray, Jimmy and Jean Cheatham, Richard Berry, Ernie K-Doe, Fats Waller, John Lee Hooker, Little Richard, B.B. King, Lionel Hampton, Jimmy Reed, and Count Basie. Otis talks about playing a lewd record by accident, meeting Fats Waller, and tells the story of how he cussed out Count Basie on the phone by accident.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Count Basie, Don & Dewey, Johnny Otis Show, Jimmy McCracklin, Etta James, Roy Hamilton, T-Bone Walker, Aretha Franklin, Jimmy Witherspoon, Dixie Hummingbirds, Billie Holiday, and Big Maybelle. Otis promotes some upcoming gigs.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-09-10; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2509; EC10 2510
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r46q97f73j
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Chuck Berry, Aretha Franklin, Drifters, Freddie King, Heartbeats, Dizzy Gillespie, Lil Green, Cadillacs, Pete Lewis, Muddy Waters, Bobby Bland, Clifton Chenier, Lloyd Price, Fats Domino, Art Tatum, Ray Charles, Roy Hamilton, Roy Milton, and Charles Brown. Otis talks about Charles Brown's debut performance in L.A. and his recording of "Drifting Blues."
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Johnny Otis, Richard Berry, Duke Ellington, LaVern Baker, Saunders King, Pointer Sisters, Jay McShann, Jimmy McCracklin, B.B. King, Jimmy Wilson, Ruth Brown, Louis Armstrong, and Robert Johnson. Otis and friends talk about blues forms in Northern and Southern California.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-09-17; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Tim "Zeke the Sheik" Dundon
      EC10 2511; EC10 2512
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/623h93p92t
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Sam & Dave, Marvin Gaye, Louis Jordan, Lester Young, Duke Ellington, Coasters, Bobbettes, Johnny Otis Show, Taj Mahal, Big Joe Turner, Aretha Franklin, Wilson Pickett, Percy Mayfield, and Ray Charles. Otis talks about environmental conservation.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Little Walter, Howlin' Wolf, James Carr, Joe Simon, Little Richard, Don & Dewey, Johnny Otis Show, Billie Holiday, Jimmie Lunceford, Fats Domino, Champion Jack Dupree, Martha & The Vandellas, Four Tops, O.V. Wright, and Ruth Brown. Otis reads an article about national parks and environmental conservation. Otis and Tim "Zeke the Sheik" Dundon talk about conservation, compost generation and usage.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-09-24; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Garfield Verdeen, Shelly Rim
      EC10 2513; EC10 2514
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/366613t901
      Tape 1 (EC 10 2513): Otis plays the music of The El Dorados, Albert King, Mar-Keys, Clifton Chenier, Clyde McPhatter, Ruth Brown, Ben E. King, Coasters, Brook Benton, Lucky Millinder & Sister Rosetta Tharpe, Nat King Cole, Temptations, Stevie Wonder, Johnny Otis, and Louis Jordan. Otis talks about putting The Coasters together. Otis and Rim talk more about Otis's new album and working together in the old days.
      Tape 2 (EC 10 2514): Otis plays the music of Muddy Waters, John Lee Hooker, Ray Charles, Aretha Franklin, Ernie K-Doe, Lee Dorsey, and previews tracks from his new album, Spirit of the Black Territory Bands.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-10-01; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2515; EC10 2516
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z60c87w48k
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Earl Bostic, LaVern Baker, Billy Preston, Donnie Hathaway, Clifton Chenier, T-Bone Walker, Johnny Otis Show, Sam Cooke, Billie Holiday, and Count Basie. Otis and friends take phone calls.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Shirley & Lee, Little Willie John, Don & Dewey, Eddie Vinson, Ben Webster, Hank Ballard & The Midnighters, Drifters, Aretha Franklin, Tyrone Davis, Willie Mabon, Washboard Sam, Teen Queens, Lionel Hampton, Fats Domino, Clarence "Frogman" Henry, Ray Charles, Otis Redding, Duke Ellington, Mills Brothers, B.B. King, and Jimmy Reed. Otis and friends talk about music today vs. African American music in the past.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Otis Career Retrospective, 1990-10-08; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Tom Morgan
      EC10 2517; EC10 2518
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x21t44w331
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of The Drifters, Jimmy Reed, Chuck Berry, Jimmy Nelson, Big Maybelle, T-Bone Walker, Sam & Dave, Don Covay, Nat Cole & Johnny Mercer, Ray Charles, Stevie Wonder, Junior Walker & The All Stars, Albert Ammons & Meade Lux Lewis, Elmore James, and Little Milton. Otis tells stories about Big Maybelle and how T-Bone Walker convinced Otis to start singing, about playing with Albert Ammons, Meade Lewis, and Pete Johnson, and then introduces a recorded interview he did Armed Forces Radio.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of J. Otis, Aretha Franklin, Otis Redding, King Curtis, Billie Holiday, and Edmond Hall. Otis talks about how he got started in music with "Count" Otis Matthews and other bands, his first recordings (including "Harlem Nocturne"), his band's first tour, the shift towards smaller R&B combos, the Barrelhouse, and meeting Little Esther Phillips. Otis and Morgan talk about Otis's upcoming album.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-10-15; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2519; EC10 2520
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j92g25f178
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Muddy Waters, Big Joe Turner, Count Basie, Billie Holiday, Leonard Bernstein, Ray Charles, Marvin Gaye, Martha & The Vandellas, Hank Williams, Bo Diddley, Charlie Parker, Ella Fitzgerald, Elmore James, Bobby Bland, Drifters, and Percy Mayfield. Ken McKnight promotes a benefit concert for medical shipments to Trinidad and Tobago.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Louis Jordan & J. Otis, Fats Domino, Etta James, Chuck Berry, Jimmy Reed, Smokey Hogg, B.B. King, Aretha Franklin, T-Bone Walker, Bob Crosby, Coleman Hawkins, Stevie Wonder, Four Tops, Jerry Lee Lewis, and Little Richard. Otis talks about energy conservation and composting biodegradable materials.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-10-22; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Billy Vera
      EC10 2521; EC10 2522
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/w12z113749
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Big Joe Turner, Fats Domino, John Lee Hooker, Jimmie Lunceford, Little Willie John, B.B. King, LaVern Baker, Dizzy Gillespie, Chuck Willis, Staple Singers, Don & Dewey, Frankie Lymon & The Teenagers, and Rascals. Otis and Vera talk about Art Blakey, Vera's TV bandleader job, Black territory bands, playing at the Apollo Theater, and Frankie Lymon.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of The Coasters, Moonglows, Otis Redding, Percy Mayfield, Elmore James, Clyde McPhatter & The Drifters, Todd Rhodes, Ruth Brown, Robert Johnson, and Billie Holiday. Otis and Vera talk about Duke Ellington and Bonnie Raitt.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990-11-05; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2523; EC10 2524
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j23603x12v
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of The Mills Brothers, Duke Ellington, Fontella Bass, Ben E. King, Junior Walker & The All Stars, Sam & Dave, Curtis Mayfield & The Impressions, Edwin Star, Earl Bostic, Johnny Otis Show, Charlie Parker, Billie Holiday, Paul Kelly, Mar-Keys, Muddy Waters, John Lee Hooker, Joe Liggins, and Frank Culley.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Richard Berry, Ray Charles, Jessie Hill, John Lee Hooker, Coasters, King Curtis, Aretha Franklin, Stevie Wonder, Jimmy Ruffin, Lee Allen, Little Willie John, Nat Cole, Art Tatum & Ben Webster, Otis Redding, and Howard Tate.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1991-04-06; 3 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Tom McElhaney
      EC10 3670; EC10 3671; EC10 3672
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/q47r66qk2d
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Inez & Charlie Foxx, Four Deuces, Big Jay McNeely, Bull Moose Jackson, Ivory Joe Hunter, Wilbert Harrison, Big Mama Thornton, Hank Williams, Dinah Washington, Soul Stirrers, Billie Holiday, Joe Turner and Wynonie Harris, and T-Bone Walker. Otis and friends chat about Ivory Joe Hunter, how Bull Moose Jackson got his name, meeting Hank Williams in 1950 and how many African Americans are country western music fans, especially in the South.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of The Ikettes, Jay McShann & Walter Brown, Katie Webster, Brenton Wood, Lester Young, Martha & The Vandellas, Stevie Wonder, Jackie Wilson, Sonny Boy Williamson, Mercy Dee, Fats Domino, and Young Jessie. Otis talks about working with Lester Young, about going to jail and police brutality, then chats with friends about Celtic art, cultures, and Dorothy Donegan.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Hank Ballard & The Midnighters, Etta James, Chuck Berry, June Richmond, Elmore James, Marvin & Johnny, John Lee Hooker, Big Maybelle, Fats Waller, Spiders, Richard Berry, Slim Harpo, Monotones, El Dorados, Aretha Franklin, and Jesse Belvin. Otis promotes an upcoming gig.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Girl Vocal Groups Night, 1990?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Ray Campi
      EC10 2682
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/049g15j60v
      Otis plays the music of Muddy Waters, Howlin' Wolf, Billie Holiday, Fats Waller, Sweet Inspirations, Bukka White, B.B. King, Supremes, Martha & The Vandellas, Janettes, Chiffons, Huey "Piano" Smith, Ernie K-Doe, Sixteens, Laura Otis, Shondells, Bobbettes, Teen Queens, Otisettes, Staple Singers, Shirelles, Patti LaBelle & The Blue Belles, Bunny Siegler, Billy Stewart, and Aretha Franklin. Otis takes phone calls and chats with Ray Campi about rockabilly and Rose Maddox and her upcoming gig.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1990?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Brad Pie
      EC10 3676
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x11x41td2f
      Otis plays the music of Chuck Berry, Eddie "Cleanhead" Vinson, B.B. King, Lionel Hampton, Marvelettes, Joe Turner, Ernie K-Doe, James Brown, Jimmy Reed, Duke Ellington, T-Bone Walker, Ray Charles, and Aretha Franklin. Live blues performance by Brad Pie. Otis takes phone calls.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Ray Charles Special, 1991-05-25; 3 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Bob Kinnard, Tony Segunda
      EC10 3673; EC10 3674; EC10 3675
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r96712sg2k
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Ray Charles, Ben Webster, Clifton Chenier, J. and Shuggie Otis, Roy Hamilton, Sam & Dave, Charles Brown, Preston Love, Marvin & Johnny, Bo Diddley, Lloyd Price, Duke Ellington and Louis Armstrong, and T-Bone Walker. Otis talks about the Berkeley Farmer's Market, the Ecology Center, and radical vegetable gardening with Kinnard and Segunda.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Ray Charles, J. Otis with Ramona, Ruth Brown, Sonny Criss, and Little Willie John. Otis talks more with guests about growing trees, organic gardening, composting and chickens.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of the Impressions, Jay McShann, Jack McVea, Johnny Ace, Mary Wells, Paul Williams, Lucky Millinder, Marvelettes, Little Milton, Louis Jordan, Billie Holiday, Ella Fitzgerald & Louis Armstrong, Clyde McPhatter, John Lee Hooker, Coasters, Martha & The Vandellas, and Jimmie Lunceford,
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1991?; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 3677; EC10 3678
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/534f661h5s
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Bobby Bland, Ike & Tina Turner, Otis Redding, Count Basie, John Lee Hooker, Ray Charles, Lightnin' Hopkins, Midge Williams, Muddy Waters, Slim Gaillard, and Aretha Franklin. Otis talks about his upcoming all-day radio show fundraiser, Dizzy Gillespie, having a second chance at life and enjoying the good things.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Jimmy Reed, Percy Mayfield, Spirits of Rhythm, Professor Longhair, Martha & The Vandellas, Bill Doggett, Elmore James, Chuck Berry, Dizzy Gillespie, Billie Holiday, Johnny Otis, and Tony Allen. Otis talks about Leo Watson and the Spirits of Rhythm.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Duke Ellington Special, 1992-04-24; 1 Audiocassette; Featured guest(s): Charles "Sumo" Schofner, Dr. George Curtis
      cass 991
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c28950b357
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Martha Reeves, Temptations, Ray Charles, Duke Ellington, Aretha Franklin, Otis Redding, Blind Willie McTell, John Lee Hooker, Slim & Slam, El Dorados, and Jimmy Reed. Otis talks about touring experiences, the birth of his daughter, and Duke Ellington with Charles "Sumo" Schofner.